

## **SOFTWARE DEVELOPER**

**SOFTWARE ENGINEER** 

## ESTEBAN PEDRAZA

## CONTACT

epedrazasolano@gmail.com

www.estebanpedraza.co

in linkedin.com/in/estebanpedraza

## TECHNOLOGIES

- HTML / CSS
- Bootstrap
- Angular 10+
- Angular Js
- JavaScript
- Git / GitHub
- SQL (Server, MySQL, Oracle)
- WordPress
- Java
- NodeJS
- C++
- C#
- Python
- Azure Cloud

#### LANGUAGES

- English | B2 Intermediate
- Spanish | C2 Native

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I'm a software developer with two years of experience working with development and mainteinance of websites and platforms for companies and institutions. I have worked and certified my experience with technologies such as Angular 10+, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, NodeJS and Java and therefore I'm available to work as a Front-end or Back-end developer.

## EXPERIENCE

#### **Junior Software Developer - Bex Technology S.A.**

NOVEMBER 2019 - FEBRUARY 2021

- Front-end development of websites and platforms with MVC design patterns using technologies such as AngularJS, Angular 10+, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap y JavaScript.
- Data layer persistence using DBMS such as SQL Server and Oracle Server.
- Platform development using lists, libraries and active directory with Microsoft technologies such as Azure and Sharepoint.

#### Software Developer UI - Kantar Media

JUNE 2021 - AUGUST 2021

- Front-end and Back-end development of websites and platforms with MVC design patterns using Angular 10+, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript.
- Back-end maintenance of web platforms with technologies such as NodeJS.
- Data layer persistence using DBMS such as SQL Server and Oracle Server.

#### **Java Developer - Globant Colombia**

NOVEMBER 2021 - MARCH 2022

- Platform maintenance with microservices architecture based on NodeJS, Docker, Kubernetes and MySQL...
- Front-end maintenance of web platforms with Angular 10+.

# WHAT CHARACTERIZES ME?

- Quick adaption to the work environment.
- Never stop learning.
- Always looking to form new connections and grow.

#### LEARNING PATH

**Data Science with Python** *Platzi | In progress* 

Al and ML with Python

Platzi | Pending

#### HOBBIES



## EDUCATION

#### Pontificia Universidad Javeriana - Bogotá

JANUARY 2018 - DECEMBER 2023

- Implement software projects using design patterns.
- Perform and automate unit tests of software with JUnit and Sellenium.
- Design and construction of RestFul APIs.
- Knowledge about data structures and their usefulness to organize information as required.

#### Servicio Nacional de Aprendizaje

JANUARY 2014 - DECEMBER 2015

• Build software from the requirements analysis bases, through design to implementation in real work environments.

## CERTIFICATIONS

Angular 10+ Course

Udemy | November 2020

Git/GitHub Course

Udemy | November 2020

MySQL Bootcamp Course

Udemy | December 2020

**NodeJS Course** 

Udemy | December 2020

Security management in Azure

IT Talent - Microsoft Partner | May 2020

#### **EVENTS I'VE BEEN PART OF**

Facebook Developers Hackaton | 2° Place February 2021

IBM - IEEE Bootcamp: Journey to CFC April 2021